嘿 艾迪
Hey, Eddie. Aah!
你在这里做什么?      没事 看你睡觉
What are you doing here?        Nothing roomie, just watching you sleep.
为什么?
Why?
那让我觉得很平静
It makes me feel, urn, peaceful.
请继续
Ha. ha. Ahem. Please.
我现在没法睡了
I can't sleep now!
你要我唱歌给你听吗?
Oh, you want me to sing?
不 听着
No. Look.
够了 我要你立刻离开这间公寓
That's it. It's over. I want you out. I want you out of the apartment now!
你在胡说什么?
Oh, what, what, what are you talking about?
人魔汉尼拔
Hannibal Lecter?
他比你更适合当室友
Better roommate than you.
不
No.
我觉得你不公平 某天晚上你看到我被吓到了
See now, I don't think you're being fair. I mean one night you see me, you get scared.
那你没看到我的那些晚上呢?
I mean what about the other nights when you don't see me, huh?
昨晚你起床喝水
What about last night you went and got some water...
我好心躲在门后 那又怎么说?
and I was nice enough to hide behind the door. What's that about, huh?
我不知道
I didn't realize that.
马上滚出去!
Get out now!
好吧 你真的要我滚吗?
Okay. You really want me out?
对 请滚
Yes, please.
我要听你说你要我滚
Then I want to hear you say. I want to hear you say "you want me out".
我要你滚
I want you out.
不不不 我要听你亲口说
No no no. I want to hear it from your lips.
那之前你从哪儿听到的?
Where'd you hear it before?
好吧 你知道么? 就当我已经滚了
Oh, right, all right. You know what pal? Consider me gone.
明天你下班回来会发现我不在了
You know what? I'll be out by the time you get home from work tomorrow.
谢谢      我听到了
Thank you.        I heard that.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第19集
艾迪不想走 The One Where Eddie Won't Go
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
谢谢      嗨
Thanks.        Hey.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
看看你
Well, look at you!
终于把时光机修好了?
Finally got that time machine working, huh?
真的 你们喜欢么?
Seriously, you like it?
有个家伙在卖衣服
This guy was selling them
在第八大道 然后我就想
on 8th Avenue, and I thought
你知道我没有什么吗?      镜子?
You know what I don't have?        A mirror?
好吧 尽管笑吧 我觉得很潇洒
Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.
哇 对于一个
Wow! For a guy
刚失业的人来说 你的心情真不错
who's recently lost his job, you're in a awfully good mood.
我会没事的 我又不是从头开始
Hey I'll be all right. I mean it's not like I'm starting from square one.
我是"我们的日子"里的德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray on Days of our Lives.
那肯定可以算是一种储备吧
Huh? I mean that's got to have some kind of cachet.
储备? 潇洒?
Cachet? Jaunty?
钱德送我每日一词卫生纸
Chandler gave me word-of-the-day toilet paper
我去买杯咖啡
I'm gonna get some coffee.
嗨      嗨
Hey        Hey.
哦 怎么样? 你看那本书了么?
Oh! So so so, did you read the book?
天啊 太不可思议了
Oh, my God. It was incredible!
对吧 是不是完全说中你的心声了?
Didn't it, like, totally speak to you?
这是什么样的书?
Whoa, whoa, what book is this?
瑞秋 你一定要看这本书 书名是"掌握自己的风"
Uh! You have to read this book. It's called Be Your Own Wind Keeper
是写女人需要拥有更多权力
It's about how women need to become more empowered.
对 但是有风
Yeah and oh! But there's wind.
风让我们成为女神
And the wind can make us goddesses.
你知道谁把我们的风抢走了吗?
Do you know who takes our wind?
男人 他们就这样拿走了
Men. They just take it.
男人抢走风了?
Men just take our wind?
一直都是 因为他们是闪电使者
Uh-huh. All the time. Because they are the lightning bearers.
哇噢
Wow.
听起来很酷 有点像霍比特人
That sounds kind of cool, kind of like The Hobbit.
一点都不像霍比特人
It is nothing like The Hobbit.
它像是看穿了我曾经有过的每一段关系
It's like reading about every relationship I've ever had.
理查除外
Except for Richard.
是的 理查绝对不会偷走你的风
Oh, yes. No. Richard would never steal your wind.
没错      没错
No.        No.
因为他很可口      没错
Because he's yummy.        Yes.
但其他男人就会
But all the other ones.
嗯 对了 有一段写他们总是
Oh yes. Oh, and the part about how they're always
吸走我们储存的内在力量
drinking from our pool of inner power
但上帝禁止我们使用内在力量
But God forbid we should take a sip.
谁要吃长条糕?
Anybody want a cruller?
这是闪电使者的典型做法
Ok, this is a typical lightning bearer thing.
那像是 额
Right there. It's like, urn...
"嗨 谁要吃我的老二形蛋糕"?
"Hello. Who wants one of my phallic shaped man cakes?"
别担心 事情已经发生了
Don't worry about it already! Things happen.
所以你不气我被炒鱿鱼?
So you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?
乔伊 看着我
Joey, look at me.
看着我
Look at me!
我的牙齿沾到口红了吗?
Do I have lipstick on my teeth?
没有
No.
我们能继续谈我的问题吗?
Uh, can we get back to me?
听着亲 在这一行到处有人被炒鱿鱼
Look, honey. People get fired left and right in this business.
我已经帮你争取到"另一个世界"的试镜
I already got you an audition for Another World.
太棒了
All right!
二号出租车司机?
"Cab Driver Number two?"
不客气
You're welcome.
但我演过德瑞克雷莫端医生
But, but I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
我怎么能从神经外科医生变成开出租的?
How can I go from being a neurosurgeon to driving a cab?
世事无常 随遇而安吧
Things change. Roll with them.
但这个角色只有两句台词
But this is a two line part!
这就像是在开倒车
It's like taking a step backwards.
我不要做这个
I'm not gonna do this.
乔伊
Joey.
我要跟你说我跟阿尔明查
I'm gonna tell you the same thing I told Al Minza
和他的狗狗金字塔说一样的话
and his pyramid of dogs.
有工作就做 别在地上拉粑粑
Take any job you can get, and don't make on the floor.
对不起
I'm sorry.
再见
I'll see you.
天啊
Uh, God!
天啊 我是说它真的
Oh, God! I mean it's just so...
对吧?
Isn't it?
这像是在看我自己的一生
Uh. This is like reading about my own life!
这本书应该叫"掌握自己的风 瑞秋"
I mean this book could have been called Be Your Own Wind Keeper Rachel!
我觉得虽然不会卖一百万本
I don't think it would have sold a million copies
但那会是送你的很不错的礼物
but it would've made a nice gift for you.
大家好      嘿
Hey, you guys.        Hey.
亲爱的 我们该走了
Uh, sweetie, we've gotta go.
不
No!
不?
No? Heh.
不 为什么我们总是得照你的时间表来做事?
No! Why do we always have to do everything according to your timetable?
事实上 是按照电影院的时间表
Actually, it's the movie theater that has the timetable.
这样你才不会错过开头
It's so you don't miss the beginning.
不 这跟电影院无关 这是关于你偷走了我的风
No. See, this isn't about the movie theater. This is about you stealing my wind.
加油 姑娘
You go, girl!
我说得不好 对吧?
I can't pull that off, can I?
对不起 你的风?
Excuse me, your, your, your wind?
对 我的风
Yes, my wind.
你不让我吹又怎么能期待长大(变大)?
How do you expect me to grow if you won't let me blow?
你知道我...
You know I don't have...
不会反对那个
have a problem with that.
好吧
Okay.
现在我只是需要独处一下
I just, I just really need to be with myself right now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗯嗯嗯?      哦对 我不必道歉
Mm, mm. mm.        Uh, you're right. I don't have to apologize.
抱歉 该死
Sorry. Damn it!
那是什么?      我不知道
What is it?        I, I don't know.
里面都是一些关于风和树
It's got all this stuff about wind and trees...
还有圣池
and there's some kind of sacred pool in it.
我不是很看得懂 但她似乎非常生气
I mean I don't really get it. But she's, she's pretty upset about it.
看 这就是为什么我不和看书的女人约会
See? This is why I don't date women who read.
额哦
Uh-oh.
什么? 那是什么?
What? What's that?
我的信用卡帐单
It's my VISA bill.
两封里的第一封
Envelope one of two.
一定不会是好事      打开 打开
That can't be good.        Open it, open it.
天啊
Oh, my God!
看看这个 我怎么会花这么多钱?
Look at this! How did I spend so much money?
乔伊 那是最低应缴额度 总额在那边
Uh, Joey, that's just the minimum amount due. That's your total due.
在原野瓷器花了3500?
Whoa, whoa. 3500 dollars at "Porcelain Safari"?
我的动物们
My animals.
店员说它们很适合我 他说话带口音 我被迷惑了
Hey the guy said they suited me. He spoke with an accent. I was all confused.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do!
我想你可以从在"另一个世界"开出租车开始
Well I guess you can start by driving a cab on Another World.
什么?      那个试镜?
What?        That audition?
那是只有两句台词的角色
That's a two line part!
乔伊 你欠"我爱树脂"1100块
Joey, you owe $1100 at "I Love Lucite".
那又怎么样?      接受吧
So what?        So suck it up, man.
那是工作 可以赚钱
It's a job. It's money.
我不需要你变得爱批评 高傲又爱卖弄学问
Hey! I don't need you getting all judgmental and condescending and pedantic.
卫生纸?      嗯
Toilet paper?        Yeah.
我不是那样的人 我只是比较现实
Look I'm not being any of those things. Okay? I'm being realistic.
别说了 你是我的朋友才对      我是你的朋友
Well knock it off, you're supposed to be my friend!        I am your friend.
那你该跟我说些像"乔伊 你会没事的"
Then tell me things like, "Joey, you'll be fine."
"坚持住" "你一定会出头的 我知道"
"Hang in there" and, and  "Something big's gonna come along. I know it!"
但我不知道
But I don't know it.
我只知道你欠"缤纷世界"2300块
What I do know is that you owe $2300 at "Isn't It Chromantic"
罗斯 我知道我欠了多少钱
Hey Ross, I'm aware of what I owe.
那就理智点 你花了十年才得到那份工作
Ok, well then get some sense. I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job.
下份工作又得等多久呢?      现在我不想听这些
Who knows how long it's gonna be till you get another?        Look I don't want to hear this right now
我只是说...
I'm just saying...
别"只是说"!
Well, don't "just say"!
或许我该走了
Oh. You know, maybe, maybe I should just go.
好吧
Okay.
好的 再见
Ok, I'll see you later
考虑一下 好么?
Just think about it, okay?
我不需要考虑
I don't need to think about it!
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
那是重要角色
That was huge!
我的大好机会一定会出现 等着瞧吧
Big things are gonna happen! You'll see!
罗斯
Ross!
你还在吗?
You still there?
嘿 朋友      哦 天啊
Hey, pal.        Oh, God!
艾迪 你还在这做什么?
Eddie, what are you still doing here?
就是给一些水果蔬菜脱水
Uh, just some basic dehydrating of a few fruits and vegetables.
天啊 这真的太棒了
Man alive, this thing's fantastic!
艾迪  你是不是忘了什么?
Look Eddie, aren't you forgetting anything?
哦对 我给我们买了新的金鱼
Oh, yeah. That's right. Look, I got us a new goldfish.
他比上一只金鱼有活力多了
He's a lot feistier than the last one.
或许因为上一只金鱼是培珀莉饼干做的
Maybe because the last one was made by Pepperidge Farm.
艾迪 现在是不是还有其他什么事你忘了做?
Eddie, isn't there something else you're supposed to be doing right now?
不 除非它跟脱水有关
Wll, not unless it's got something to do with dehydrating my man
因为现在我是脱水疯子
because right now, I'm a dehydrating maniac!
你必须得帮帮我
Look you have to help me out here.
我以为我们说好了 我以为我回来时
I thought we had a deal. I thought by the time I got
你知道这是什么吗?
You know what that is?
你前室友的肾脏?
Your last roommate's kidney?
这是蕃茄
That's a tomato. Ha, ha.
这个一定要拿出来展示
This one definitely goes in the display.
阿甘 我要外带一杯柠檬汁
Hey, Gunther, let me get a, uh, lemonade to go.
柠檬汁?
Lemonade?
你没事吧?
You okay, man?
只是事业遇到点问题
Ahh, it's career stuff
我不知道你听说没 他们杀死了我的角色
I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character on the show.
那太可惜了 他们怎么做的?
Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?
我从电梯里掉下去了
I fell down an elevator shaft.
那真的很逊
Oh. That sucks.
我在雪崩时被埋了
I was buried in an avalanche.
什么?
What?
我演过"我的孩子们"里的布莱斯
I used to be Brice on All My Children.
为什么大家都要看我睡觉?
Why must everybody watch me sleep?
不准再看我睡觉了 不准!
There'll be no more watching me sleep! No more!
再看!      我...
watching!        I...
来看看 我有一些好东西要脱水 葡萄 杏桃
Hey man, check it out, I got some great stuff to dehydrate. I got some grapes, got some apricots
我觉得看这些水球会变成什么样子很酷
I thought it'd be cool to see what happens with these water balloons.
滚出去 出去出去出去...!
Get out. Get out, get out, get out...!
什么?      你 搬出去
What?        You! Move out!
带着你的水果 愚蠢的小水果 滚出去!
Take your fruit! Your stupid small fruit and get out!
你要我搬走?
You want me to move out? Uh...
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
额 我
Heh. I, uh-Ooh!
我得说 你不觉得那有点突然 你不觉得么?
Ha, ha. I gotta tell you man, I mean, that's uh, it's kind of out of the blue, I mean don't you think?
这一点都不突然
This is not out of the blue!
这完全不突然!
This is smack dab in the middle of the blue!
哇哦!
Whoa!
淡定 别激动 兄弟
Relax! Take it easy, buddy!
你不必告诉我第二次 你想我走? 好吧
You don't have to tell me twice. You want me to go? Alright, alright
我会回来拿我的东西
guess I'll be back for my stuff.
如果你以为我会让你跟我的鱼独处 你就疯了
But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish, you're insane Jack!
需要我帮忙吗?
You want some help?
我不需要帮忙 朋友
No help required, chico!
一路到机场? 那超过三十里远了
All the way to the airport, huh? You know, that's over 30 miles.
那得花你不少钱
That's gonna cost you about "so" bucks.
对不起 应该是五十块
Excuse me, that's 50 bucks.
什么?      五十块
What?        Five-O dollars.
哦 你知道是怎么回事么?
Oh. You know what it is?
传真过来的剧本字有点模糊
It's smudgy because they're fax pages.
我在"我们的日子"演德瑞克雷莫瑞医生时
When I was on Days of our Lives as Dr. Drake Ramoray...
他们会打印整个剧本寄给我
they'd send over the whole script on real paper and everything.
那真的太棒了
Ha, ha. That's great.
如果你要加戏 比如出租车发生车祸
And, and just so you know, if you wanted to expand this scene like, like have the cab crash or something
我可以治疗乘客
I could attend to the victims
因为我有演医生的背景
because I have a background in medical acting.
好吧 听着 谢谢你来试镜
Okay, listen, thanks for coming in.
不不 别谢我来试镜 至少让我演完先
No no. Uh, don't thank me for coming in. Uh, at least let me finish.
我们可以走高速
Uh, we could take the expressway
但这时你最好超预算
but, uh, this time of day you're better off taking the "budge".
应该是要过桥才对吧?
You were going for the word bridge there, weren't you?
祝我今天愉快
I'll have a good day.
好了 第28题
Okay, question number 28.
你曾让闪电使者拿走你的风吗?
"Have you ever allowed a lightning bearer to take your wind?"
我要回答"没有"
I would have to say no.
那我要说"胡扯"
And I would have to say, "Pah, ha"
什么?
What?
你不记得布偶男了吗?
Do you not remember the puppet guy?
你根本就是让他在你的内在力量池里洗脚
Yeah, you like totally let him wash his feet in the pool of your inner power.
还有他的布偶
And his puppet too!
好吧 至少我没有让男人
Yeah ok, well at least I didn't let some guy
在第一次约会时进入我的真理森林
into the forest of my righteous truth on the first date!
谁?      保罗
Who?        Paul!
哦!
Oh!
好吧 继续 下一题
Okay, okay, moving on, moving on. Next question.
好吧 第29题
Okay, number 29.
你是否曾背叛其他女神
"Have you ever betrayed another goddess
为了闪电使者? 好吧 第30题
for a lightning bearer?" Okay number 30.
哦哦哦 回到第29题
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Let's go back to 29.
额 没有...
Not, uh...
额 我不记得有
Ahem. Not to my recollection.
丹尼亚夏克 九年级
Huuh, alright, Danny Arshack, ninth grade.
瑞秋 你知道瓶口完全是指向我
Oh come on Rachel, you know the bottle was totally pointing at me.
那是因为你占了一半的圈子
Only because you took up half the circle!
看看你们两个 真是可悲
Listen to you two. It's so sad.
看起来我得一个人参加女神会议了
Looks like I'll be going to the goddess meetings alone.
你休想 当她们发现你和杰森赫利上床
Well not when they find out you slept with Jason Hurley
就在他和摩妮卡分手一个小时后
an hour after he broke up with Monica.
一小时?
One hour?
你真会挑拨离间! 哦!
You are such a leaf blower! Oh!
哦!
Ugh!
小心3D的"最后的晚餐" 犹大有点松了
Oh, hey, uh, be careful with that 3D Last Supper. Judas is a little loose.
天啊 发生了什么事?
Oh, my God! What's going on?
他们要把我的东西都收回去 我想你说得对
They're taking all my stuff back. I guess you were right.
不 我错了 所以我来找你
No, look I wasn't right. That's what I came here to tell you.
那天我满脑子只想着自己的事
I was totally hung up on my own stuff the other day.
不 听着 我是那种需要安全感的人 知道么
No listen. I'm someone who needs the whole security thing, you know?
知道下一笔收入在哪里 但你不需要那样
To know exactly where my next paycheck is coming from. But you, you don't need that.
那真的让我很佩服
And that's amazing to me.
我永远都没办法跟你一样 乔伊
I could never do what you do, Joey.
谢谢 罗斯      你得为更好的机会坚持住
Thanks Ross.        Yeah. And you should hold out for something bigger
我无法告诉你我多么尊重
I can't tell you how much respect I have
你不去参加那个愚蠢的出租车司机试镜
for you not going to that stupid cab driver audition.
我去了      太棒了 结果如何?
I went.        Great! How did it go?
我没拿到角色      你是好样的!
I didn't get it.        Good for you!
什么?      你在实现梦想
What?        You're living the dream!
啊?
Huh?
好吧
All right, then!
哦 别拿走我的鹦鹉      什么?
Oh, not my parrot.        What?
我看不下去了
I can't watch this.
等一下 等等
Hey, hold on, hold on.
多少钱 那只鸟要多少钱?
How much for the, uh...? How much to save the bird?
1200      美金?
Twelve hundred.        Dollars?
你花1200块买只塑料的鸟?
You spent $1200 on a plastic bird?
那是一时冲动买的 它就在收银台附近
Uh, it was an impulse buy. Near the register.
走吧 把鸟拿走吧
Go aheah. Go ahead with the bird.
有没有200左右的东西?
It's ok. Do you have anything for around $200?
那只狗
The dog.
那个?      对
Huh?        Yeah.
我买了
I'll take it.
这是我送你的礼物
My gift to you, man.
谢谢你 罗斯
Thanks, Ross!
但我真的喜欢那只鸟
I really liked that bird, though.
不过狗也可以      对吧?
But the dog! Oh!        Yeah. Right?
这是你们的蛋糕
Here are your cakes.
我们没有点蛋糕
We didn't order cake.
对 我知道 我请客
No, I know. Ahem. They're from me.
姑娘们 这不是件好事
Look you guys, this is not good.
男人偷走我们的风已经够麻烦了
I mean we have enough trouble with guys stealing our wind
我们不该彼此对立
without taking it from each other
你说的对      你知道吗?
You're right.        You know?
我爱你们这些女神
I love you goddesses.
我爱你们
I love you.
我不想再抢你的风了
I don't ever want to suck your wind again.
谢谢 那我们没事了吧?      我们和好了
Thank you. So are we good?        Oh. We're good.
我们没事了吧?      是的
We're good?        Yes.
好吧 我得把蛋糕收回去 他们会扣我的薪水
Okay. Let me take these cakes back. Because they're gonna take that out of my paycheck.
叮咚 那个疯子走了
Ding dong, the psycho's gone!
这次你确定吗?      是的
Are you sure this time?        Yes.
是的 我确实看到他离开了
Yes, I actually saw him leave.
那家伙站在窗户那 拿着一颗人头
I mean that guy is standing in the window holding a human head.
他在拿着一个人头!
He's standing in the window holding a human head!
看看 兄弟
Check it out, man!
我在梅西百货后面的巷子里从假人身上拔下来的
I tore it off a mannequin in the alley behind Macy's. Ha, ha.
梅西百货后面没有巷子
There is no alley behind Macy's.
我在少女部偷来的 有区别么
So I got it in the junior miss department. Big diff
无论如何
Anyway check it out man.
这样我们下次办鸡尾酒会就有得聊了 兄弟
It's gonna make a hell of a conversation piece at our next cocktail party, huh pal?
我们下一次办鸡尾酒会?
Our next cocktail party?
对 我们可以把薯片放进去 让它变成薯片姑娘
Yeah, you know, we'll put chips in it. We'll make it a chip chick.
艾迪 你记得昨天吗?
Eddie, do you remember yesterday?
对 我依稀还记得
Uh, yes, I think I vaguely recall it.
你记得昨天你跟我说话吗?
Ahem. Do you remember talking to me yesterday?
对
Uh, yes.
发生了什么事?
So, what happened?
我们开车到拉斯维加斯
We took a road trip to Las Vegas man!
天啊
Oh sweet Moses
拉斯维加斯旅行 那你们有赢钱么?
So on this road trip, uh, did you win any money?
我输光了 但21点先生 他手气可好了
Nah, I crapped out. But Mr 21 over here! He cleans up!
三百块 他还买了双新鞋送我 体贴吧
$300! Check it out. He buys me these new shoes. Sweet. huh?
太棒了
Nice.
楼上见 大家再见
Uh, see you upstairs. See you, pals!
有人开始喜欢他了吗?
Is anyone else starting to really like him?
有什么能帮你么?
May I help you?
为什么我的钥匙不能用? 我的东西为什么在楼下?
Why doesn't my key work, and what's my stuff doing downstairs?
对不起
I'm sorry. Aah.
我们认识吗?
Have we met?
我是艾迪 变态 你的室友
It's Eddie, you freak! Your roommate.
对不起
I'm sorry, I, uh...
我已经有室友了
I already have a roommate.
你好
Hello.
他住在这里很多年了 我不知道你到底在说什么
Urn, he's lived here for years. I don't, I don't know what you're talking about man.
不不 他是 额
No, no. He's, uh...
不 他搬出去了 我搬进来
No, he, he moved out and I moved in.
我想我们会记得那种事
Well, I think we'd remember something like that.
我知道我会记得
I know I would. Ha, ha.
有点道理 额
That's, uh, a good point. Urn...
好吧
Okay, wow. Huh.
我想我走错公寓了
I guess I got the wrong apartment.
听着 我...
Look, I'm
真的很抱歉      没关系
I am terribly sorry.        Hey, no problem.
再见
See you.
再见 脱水水果变态狂
Goodbye, you fruit drying psychopath.
要我帮你把东西拿出来吗?
You want me to help you unpack stuff?
不用了 我自己可以
Nah, I'm okay. Oh, and, uh...
你知道 我搬回来不是因为我走投无路
Just so you know, I'm not moving back in because I have to.
我的确走投无路 可是...
I mean, I do have to, but...
只是因为那个地方不是...
It's just that that place wasn't really...
这是...
I mean this is...
欢迎回家 兄弟
Welcome home, man.
玩一下足球台?      当然
A little foos?        Absolutely!
足球怎么了?
What happened to the foosball?
那是哈蜜瓜
It's a cantaloupe.
每次罗斯过来我们都得把这个搬出来么?
Hey look, are we gonna bring this out every time Ross comes over?
他付了很多钱买下它的
He paid a lot of money for it.
我要换个方向拿      好的
I'm gonna hold him a different way.        All right.
我不理解 如果你那么讨厌它 开始为什么要买它?
I don't understand. If you hated it so much, why'd you buy it in the first place?
我有一个瓷器动物园在那里
Well, I had a whole ceramic zoo thing going over there.
但现在少了其他的动物 看起来怪怪的
But now without the other ones, it just looks tacky.
它会用马桶还是会到处留下瓷器粑粑?
Is he house trained or will he leave little bathroom tiles all over place?
别动
Stay.
Uh, stay!
好乖的假狗狗
Good fake dog.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧